

Rubi Kuo

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Profile

Ambitious front end developer with 8 years of work experiences in international projects and 2 year experiences in web development and UX design.

Quick learner, goal oriented, curious and problem solving person looking for new challenges.

LANGUAGE

Mandarin
English
Swedish
French



CONTACT INFORMATION

Helsingborg, Sweden

+46-765011688

✓ rubitiara@gmail.com

https://github.com/rubikuo

in www.linkedin.com/in/rubikuo

Новву







Travel Pho

Photography Yoga

EDUCATION

2020.09 - 2021.05 Front End Development

HBG Works, Helsingborg

Intern. Developing prototypes

connected to Helsingborgs stad's work with the innovation initiatives of H22.

2019 - 2021.06 Front End Development

EC Utbildning, Helsingborg

Enhancing skills in JavaScript by focusing on React.js, testing, UX design,

backend developement.

Front End Development

Komvux, Helsingborg

6 month intensive course in HTML,

CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap,

Jquery, Angular, API, GitHub, CLI,

Scrum, FireBase.

2005 - 2009 B.A. Radio, Television and Film

Shih Hsin Univerisity, Taipei Taiwan

GPA 3.9 (av 4)

Portfolio

https://rubikuo.surge.sh

COMPETENCIES

HTML	React.js	Scrum	Team Work
CSS/SASS	Angular	Photoshop	Coordination
jQuery	Node.js	Adobe XD	Communication
JavaScript	MongoDB	Illustrator	CRM

WORK EXPRERIENCE

Customer Relationship Management 2009-2017

- International sales.
- Worked with external customer service and internal departments to ensure every commercial project reached its goal and was completed according to plan.
- Managed social media marketing.

See appendix for more details.

<< Annex >>

Rubi Kuo

FRONT END DEVELOPER

AWARDS / ACTIVITY

Last Mile Hack

DAPP - Delivery App

- 2019 Helsingborg, Sweden
- Taiwan Women's Hockey
 Women's AHF Cup

Coordinator, Tour Leader

- 2016 Bangkok, Thailand
- Shih Hsin Delegation Member

International academic exchange 2009 Beijing, China

2008 Boston, Missouri, Michigan, U.S.A.

ADDITIONAL COURSE

- 2019 2020
 - SAS
- 💄 Hermods Helsingborg
- 2018

SFI

- 💄 Folkuniversitetet, Helsingborg
- **2**013 2014

French

I.F.C.A.D. Brussels, Belgium

Volunteer

2010 Taiwan International Documentary Festival

English Host

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 International Operations Coordinator

Orien Trading Corp., Taiwan

Coordinated triangular trading processes and maintained supplier and customer relationships with the help of strong communication and coordination skills.

2015 -2017 International Operations Coordinator

Damei Travel Service Co. Ltd, Taiwan

Reduced costs by 10-15% for each group trip by renegotiating hotel and event contracts in line with company policy, financing and terms.

2013-2014 PR & Marketing Coordinator

Dechamps-Presse SPRL, Brussels, Belgium

Maintained and managed social media, advertising and marketing tactics, to achieve exposure goals to public.

2012-2013 International Sales Coordinator

Taiwan Nanotechnology Corp., Taiwan

Worked with external customer service and internal organizational companies to ensure that each of the commercial projects met the objectives and was completed according to plan.

2009-2015 Freelance Communication Coordinator

Provided communication and coordination services at international exhibitions and activities throughout Asia:

2015 KBC Fair Shanghai, China

2015 Timtos Fair Taipei, Taiwan

2012 Gifts and Premium Fair, Hong Kong

2012 Beabi Company, Manila, Philippines

2011 Marlboro Footwear Ltd, China

2009-2011 International Sales Coordinator

Trade Way Company, Taiwan

Increased customer base by 10% in one year.